WEWERE IN ASTORE
AND A GUY IN THAT STORE
TOLD US TO PUT
OUR UNIFORMS ON.
"WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?"
HE SAYS...
THE USA IS IN
A WAR WITH JAPAN.
WE COULDN'T
BELIEVE IT.
WELL. OUR COUNTRY
WAS ATTACKED.
IT'S DIFFERENT.
IT WASN'T LIKE
KOREA OR VIETNAM.
WE WAS ATTACKED.
AND. YOU KNOW.
IT WAS A FEELING THAT...
MAYBE. WE'RE JUST
DUMB COUNTRY PEOPLE BUT.
WHERE I COME FROM. BUT.
A LOT OF US VOLUNTEERED.
WHO WOULD LIKE TO VOLUNTEER
FOR THE TANK CORPS?
FOR THE AIR FORCE?
WHO WOULD LIKE TO VOLUNTEER
FOR THE NAVY OR WHATEVER?
AND THEN. THEY SAID.
"WHO WOULD LIKE TO VOLUNTEER
FOR THE AIRBORNE?"
SOMEBODY SAYS. "WHAT THE
HELL'S THE AIRBORNE?"
NOBODY EVER HEARD OF IT.
WE CAME FROM
A SMALL. SMALL TOWN
AND THREE FELLAS IN THAT TOWN
WERE. THAT WERE "4F".
COMMITTED SUICIDE
BECAUSE THEY COULDN'T GO.
A DIFFERENT TIME.
I DID THINGS.
I DIDN'T DO 'EM
FOR MEDALS.
FOR ACCOLADES.
I DID 'EM BECAUSE
IT'S WHAT HAD TO BE DONE.
THE GUY SAYS. "WOULD YOU
JUMP OUT OF AIRPLANES?
"YOU KNOW. YOU GOT
ALL YOUR ARMY EQUIPMENT
AND YOU JUMP OUT OF AIRPLANES.
TO FIGHT THE ENEMY."
THESE GUYS. THEY SAID.
"GO TO HELL".
NOBODY PUT UP
THEIR HANDS.
AND THEN. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT WAS BROUGHT IT UP.
BUT THE GUY GIVING
THE SPEECH WAS SAYING.
"BUT YOU GET PAID
$50 A MONTH MORE."
SO. THAT MADE IT
A HUNDRED BUCKS.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
( hattering )
( male )
I WANT A WHlFF
OF CHlCKEN PlE.
( male )
OKAY. BOYS. LET'S
GET THlS GEAR STOWED.
FOX COMPANY.
WE GO lN FlVE.
( male )
lN THE NAME OF THE FATHER
AND THE SON AND OF THE HOLY...
( male )
1st PLATOON
DRAW SMALL ARMS.
DO YOU NEED A HAND.
LlEUTENANT?
( male )
"EASY COMPANY!"
LlSTEN UP!
GATHER UP AROUND ME.
JUST MOVE lT UP.
C'MON. GENTLEMEN.
LET'S GO!
NOW. THE CHANNEL COAST lS
SOCKED lN WlTH RAlN AND FOG.
HlGH WlNDS ON
THE DROP ZONE.
NO JUMP TONlGHT.
THE lNVASlON
HAS BEEN POSTPONED.
WE'RE ON A 24
HOUR STAND-DOWN.
SONOFABlTCH.
DRlLL SERGEANTS.
TAKE CHARGE.
Well. this is
quite a surprise.
Not particularly.
It so happens
I rather expected it
Well. I can't
see how you people
can pass up $80.000
for the cause.
For whose cause?
If you're so interested
in serving a cause.
why don't you
join the army?
Oh...
I THlNK
lT'S CLEARlNG UP.
YOU THlNK
lT'S CLEARlNG UP?
NO.
I THlNK
lT'S CLEARlNG UP.
HOW ARE YOUR MEN?
THEY'LL BE FlNE.
FlVE O'CLOCK
lN NEW YORK.
FOUR O'CLOCK
lN CHlCAGO.
HAPPY HOUR. HUH?
YEAH.
HAPPY HOUR.
A COUPLE OF DRlNKS.
MAYBE AN EARLY DlNNER
BEFORE THE THEATER.
A ClVlLlZED PLACE
FOR ClVlLlZED MEN.
SHOULD'VE BEEN
BORN EARLlER. NlX.
WHAT. AND GlVE
UP ALL THlS?
WE'LL GO TO CHlCAGO.
l'LL TAKE YOU THERE.
YEAH.
WE'LL SEE.
ACTUALLY. YOU KNOW
WHO'S FROM THERE?
WHO?
OH. HlM.
712 DAYS OF THAT
SONOFABlTCH AND
HERE WE ARE.
( flies buzzing )
YOU PEOPLE ARE AT
THE POSlTlON OF ATTENTlON.
PRlVATE PERCONTE.
HAVE YOU BEEN
BLOUSlNG YOUR TROUSERS
OVER YOUR BOOTS
LlKE A PARATROOPER?
NO. SlR.
THEN EXPLAlN
THE CREASES
AT THE BOTTOM.
NO EXCUSE. SlR.
VOLUNTEERlNG FOR THE
PARACHUTE lNFANTRY lS
ONE THlNG. PERCONTE.
BUT YOU'VE GOT A LONG WAY TO
PROVE THAT YOU BELONG HERE.
YOUR WEEKEND PASS
lS REVOKED.
NAME?
LUZ. GEORGE.
DlRT lN THE REAR
SlDE APERTURE.
PASS REVOKED.
WHEN DlD YOU SEW
ON THESE CHEVRONS.
SERGEANT LlPTON?
YESTERDAY. SlR.
LONG ENOUGH
TO NOTlCE THlS.
REVOKED.
SlR.
NAME?
MALARKEY. DONALD G.
MALARKEY?
MALARKEY'S SLANG
FOR BULLSHlT.
lSN'T lT?
YES. SlR.
RUST ON THE BUTT
PLATE HlNGE SPRlNG.
PRlVATE BULLSHlT.
REVOKED.
NAME?
LlEBGOTT.
JOSEPH D. SlR.
RUSTY BAYONET.
LlEBGOTT.
YOU WANNA
KlLL GERMANS?
YES. SlR.
NOT WlTH THlS.
I WOULDN'T TAKE THlS
RUSTY PlECE OF SHlT TO WAR.
AND I WlLL NOT TAKE YOU
TO WAR lN YOUR CONDlTlON.
NOW. THANKS TO THESE MEN
AND THElR lNFRACTlONS.
EVERY MAN lN THE COMPANY
WHO HAD A WEEKEND PASS.
HAS LOST lT.
CHANGE lNTO YOUR "PT" GEAR.
WE'RE RUNNlNG CURRAHEE.
2nd PLATOON
FALL OUT.
WE HAVE TWO MlNUTES.
FALL OUT!
I AlN'T GOlNG UP
THAT HlLL.
HEY. PERCONTE.
WHAT ARE YOU
THlNKlNG OF.
BLOUSlN' YOUR PANTS?
SHUT UP. MARTlN.
ALRlGHT?
HE GlGGED EVERYBODY.
YEAH. WELL.
YOU SHOULD KNOW BETTER.
DON'T GlVE HlM
NO EXCUSES.
EXCUSES?
WHY DON'T YOU COME HERE.
LOOK AT THESE TROUSERS.
GET DOWN AND YOU
TELL ME lF THERE'S
A CREASE ON 'EM?
ALRlGHT. LET'S GO.
ON THE ROAD lN
"PT" FORMATlON.
LET'S MOVE.
MOVE. MOVE!
PERCONTE. LET'S GO.
PERCONTE.
PRlVATE WHlTE.
WHY ARE YOU NOT
lN YOUR PT GEAR?
I ASKED YOU
A QUESTlON. PRlVATE.
OH. "EASY COMPANY".
AND WHlLE YOU'RE RUNNlNG.
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL TAKE YOUR DAMES
TO THE MOVlES FOR YOU.
YEAH. GOOD. THEY NEED
SOME FEMALE COMPANY.
( male )
WHERE DO WE RUN?
( together )
CURRAHEE.
AND WHAT DOES
"CURRAHEE" MEAN?
WE STAND ALONE.
HOW FAR UP.
HOW FAR DOWN?
THREE MlLES UP.
THREE MlLES DOWN.
AND WHAT COMPANY
lS THlS?
"EASY COMPANY."
AND WHAT DO WE DO?
STAND ALONE.
DO NOT HELP
THAT MAN!
THAT MAN.
WE DO NOT STOP.
YOU'VE GOT 30 MlNUTES TO GET
TO THE TOP OF THlS MOUNTAlN
IF YOU WANNA SERVE
lN THE PARATROOPERS.
Hl-HO. SlLVER!
C'MON. YOU CAN
MAKE lT UP THERE.
C'MON.
C'MON NOW. C'MON.
ALLEY. LET'S GO.
C'MON. GUARNERE.
CHRlSTENSON.
C'MON.
I NEVER THOUGHT l'D SEE
THE DAY. PRlVATE WYNN.
WE ARE COMlNG ON
23 MlNUTES.
THAT MAY BE GOOD ENOUGH
FOR THE REST OF THE 506.
BUT THAT lS NOT GOOD ENOUGH
FOR "EASY COMPANY".
WE CAN MAKE lT.
WE CAN DO THlS. C'MON.
I'M GONNA
SAY SOMETHlNG.
TO WHO?
LlEUTENANT WlNTERS.
WHAT lS lT?
PERMlSSlON TO
SPEAK. SlR?
PERMlSSlON GRANTED.
SlR. WE GOT
NlNE COMPANlES. SlR.
THAT WE DO.
WELL. HOW COME WE'RE
THE ONLY COMPANY
MARCHlNG EVERY FRlDAY NlGHT.
12 MlLES. FULL PACK.
IN THE PlTCH DARK?
WHY DO YOU THlNK.
PRlVATE RANDLEMAN?
LlEUTENANT SOBEL
HATES US. SlR.
DOES NOT HATE
"EASY COMPANY".
PRlVATE RANDLEMAN.
HE JUST HATES YOU.
THANK YOU. SlR.
HE HATES HlM BACK.
HE HATES YOU.
TOO. MUCK.
LlEUTENANT WlNTERS. I WANT
CANTEENS OUT OF BELTS
WlTH THE CAPS
UNSCREWED.
"EASY COMPANY".
CANTEENS OUT AND OPEN.
ON MY COMMAND. THEY WlLL POUR
THE CONTENTS ONTO THE GROUND.
ON THE CO's ORDER. YOU WlLL
UPEND YOUR CANTEEN.
NOW. LlEUTENANT.
POUR 'EM.
WHO lS THlS?
CHRlSTENSON.
WHY lS THERE NO WATER
lN YOUR CANTEEN?
YOU DRANK FROM YOUR
CANTEEN. DlDN'T YOU?
SlR. l--
LlEUTENANT WlNTERS.
YES. SlR.
WAS THlS MAN ORDERED
TO NOT DRlNK
FROM HlS CANTEEN
DURlNG THE FRlDAY
NlGHT MARCH?
HE WAS. SlR.
PRlVATE CHRlSTENSON.
YOU HAVE DlSOBEYED
A DlRECT ORDER.
YOU WlLL FlLL
YOUR CANTEEN
AND REPEAT ALL
12 MlLES OF THE
MARCH lMMEDlATELY.
YES. SlR.
FALL OUT!
WHAT lN THE NAME
OF GOD ARE YOU
DOlNG WlTH MY COMPANY?
YOU'RE LATE AND
YOU ALLOW TROOPERS
TO DlSOBEY
DlRECT ORDERS?
NO EXCUSE. SlR.
YOU'RE MAKlNG ME
LOOK BAD. LlEUTENANT.
THlS lS NOT
"DOG COMPANY".
"FOX COMPANY".
THlS. THlS lS
"EASY COMPANY".
AND UNDER MY COMMAND.
THlS WlLL BE THE FlRST
AND FlNEST COMPANY
lN THlS REGlMENT.
I WANT THE NAMES
OF SlX MEN.
THElR lNFRACTlONS
AND YOUR DlSClPLlNARY
RECOMMENDATlONS
ON MY DESK
BY 0130.
IS THAT CLEAR?
WHAT lNFRACTlONS.
SlR?
FlND SOME.
SO. WHAT'D YOU DO?
PlCKED SlX MEN AND
GAVE 'EM LATRlNE DUTY.
THE LUCKY SlX?
MCDONALD. TOYE.
PERCONTE.
LlPTON.
MUCK AND GUARNERE.
WHY THEM?
IT WAS THElR TURN.
SOBEL'S A GENlUS.
I HAD A HEADMASTER JUST
LlKE HlM lN PREP SCHOOL.
I KNOW THE TYPE.
LEWlS.
MlCHELANGELO'S A GENlUS.
BEETHOVEN'S A GENlUS.
YOU KNOW A MAN
lN THlS COMPANY
WHO WOULDN'T
DOUBLE-TlME CURRAHEE
WlTH A FULL PACK
JUST TO PlSS
lN THAT GUY'S
MORNlNG COFFEE?
( Sobel )
LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
STAND lN THE DOOR.
GO.
ONE THOUSAND.
TWO THOUSAND.
YOU JUST BROKE BOTH
YOUR LEGS. PRlVATE GORDON.
ARE YOU TRYlNG TO
GET YOURSELF KlLLED?
NO. SlR.
STAND lN THE DOOR.
( loud chattering )
SHlT.
TO THE WALL.
OVER AS A TEAM.
GO ON.
AGAlNST THE WALL.
JESUS. WHAT
THE HELL lS THlS?
THAT'S PlG GUTS. BOY.
GODDAMMlT!
WHY ARE YOU HERE.
PRlVATE GORDON?
I WANNA BE lN
THE AlRBORNE. SlR.
I DON'T BELlEVE YOU.
WHY ARE YOU HERE.
PRlVATE GORDON?
I WANNA BE lN
THE AlRBORNE. SlR.
YOU HAVE 50 MlNUTES
TO THE TOP AND BACK.
AND I WlLL BE
WATCHlNG YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU
WAlTlNG FOR?
"EASY COMPANY" HAS
THE FlNEST PERFORMANCE RECORD
IN THE ENTlRE
2nd BATTALlON.
I BELlEVE EVERY
BlT OF THAT lS
THANKS TO YOU.
CONGRATULATlONS.
CAPTAlN SOBEL.
THANK YOU. SlR.
ISN'T THAT
LlEUTENANT WlNTERS LEADlNG
"EASY COMPANY" lN "PT"?
YES. SlR.
HE'S A DAMNED
GOOD MAN.
I WAS PLANNlNG ON
GlVlNG HlM A SET
OF THESE TODAY.
WHY DON'T
YOU DO lT?
HE'D BE PROUD
TO GET 'EM FROM YOU.
PORNOGRAPHY.
CONTRABAND.
NON-REGULATlON CLOTHlNG.
THlS MAN HAD
200 PROPHYLACTlC KlTS
lN HlS FOOTLOCKER.
HOW lN THE NAME OF GOD WAS
HE GONNA HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO FlGHT THE WAR?
HOW lS lT PRlVATE.
PRlVATE TlPPER
HAS SPARE TlME
FOR SO MUCH
CORRESPONDENCE?
CAPTAlN. ARE
PERSONAL LETTERS TO BE
CONSlDERED CONTRABAND?
THESE MEN AREN'T
PARATROOPERS YET.
LlEUTENANT.
THEY HAVE NO
PERSONAL PROPERTY.
WHAT lS THlS?
ANYBODY?
ER. lT'S A CAN
OF PEACHES. SlR.
LlEUTENANT NlXON
THlNKS THlS lS A
CAN OF PEACHES.
THAT lS lNCORRECT.
LlEUTENANT.
YOUR WEEKEND PASS
lS CANCELLED.
THlS lS UNlTED STATES
ARMY PROPERTY
WHlCH WAS TAKEN.
WlTHOUT AUTHORlZATlON.
FROM MY MESS FAClLlTY.
AND I WlLL NOT TOLERATE
THlEVERY lN MY UNlT.
WHOSE FOOTLOCKER
lS THlS?
PRlVATE PARKES. SlR.
GET RlD OF HlM.
ALL WEEKEND PASSES
ARE CANCELLED.
OFFlCERS lNCLUDED.
CARRY ON.
LlEUTENANT WlNTERS.
COLONEL SlNK HAS SEEN
FlT TO PROMOTE YOU.
AS 1st LlEUTENANT.
YOU'LL SERVE AS MY
EXECUTlVE OFFlCER.
CONGRATULATlONS.
THANK YOU. SlR.
AND. AS A TEST OF YOUR
ORGANlZATlONAL SKlLLS
AND COMMAND POTENTlAL.
I AM DESlGNATlNG YOU...
MESS OFFlCER
FOR 14 DAYS.
REPORT TO THE MESS
KlTCHEN AT 0515 HOURS.
COMPANY BREAKFAST
TO BE SERVED AT 0600.
YES. SlR.
OH. AND. DlCK...
THERE'S RAlN
FORECAST TOMORROW.
SO. THE COMPANY WlLL
HAVE A LlGHT AFTERNOON
OF LECTURE AND
CLASSROOM lNSTRUCTlON.
I THlNK A SPEClAL MEAL
BEFORE THElR AFTERNOON OFF
WOULD BE A WELCOME
CHANGE OF PACE.
WOULD YOU AGREE?
YES. SlR.
I LlKE SPAGHETTl.
HOLD ON. MORE COMlNG.
THESE GUYS ARE
PACKlNG lT AWAY.
THlS STUFF
lS ORANGE.
SPAGHETTl AlN'T
SUPPOSED TO
BE ORANGE.
THlS AlN'T SPAGHETTl.
THlS lS ARMY NOODLES
WlTH KETCHUP.
YOU AlN'T
GOTTA EAT lT.
OH. C'MON. GONORRHEA.
AS A FELLOW lTALlAN.
YOU SHOULD KNOW
THAT CALLlNG THlS
CRAP SPAGHETTl
IS A MORTAL SlN.
YOU DON'T WANT lT.
l'LL HAVE lT.
NO. NO. NO.
l'M EATlNG HERE.
HEY. GET OUTTA HERE.
ORDERS CHANGED.
GET UP!
LECTURES
ARE CANCELLED.
"EASY COMPANY"
lS RUNNlNG UP CURRAHEE.
MOVE. MOVE!
THREE MlLES UP.
THREE MlLES DOWN.
Hl-HO. SlLVER!
LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
YOU'RE A WASHOUT.
PRlVATE HOOBLER!
YOU SHOULD PACK
UP BOTH YOUR EARS
AND GO HOME.
LOOKS LlKE
GORDON'S DONE.
AREN'T YOU. GORDON.
YOU FlNlSHED?
YOU DO NOT DESERVE
TO GET YOUR WlNGS.
PRlVATE RANDLEMAN.
YOU LOOK TlRED.
THERE'S AN AMBULANCE
WAlTlNG FOR YOU AT
THE BOTTOM OF THE HlLL.
IT CAN ALL BE
OVER RlGHT NOW.
NO MORE PAlN.
NO MORE CURRAHEE.
NO MORE
CAPTAlN SOBEL.
( chanting )
WE PULL UPON THE RlSERS.
WE FALL UPON THE GRASS.
WE NEVER LAND UPON OUR FEET.
WE ALWAYS HlT OUR ASS.
AYE. AYE. CHRlST ALMlGHTY.
WHO THE HELL ARE WE.
ZlM-ZAM. GODDAMN.
WE'RE AlRBORNE lNFANTRY.
WE PULL UPON THE RlSERS.
WE FALL UPON THE GRASS.
WE NEVER LAND UPON OUR FEET.
WE ALWAYS HlT OUR ASS.
HlDE TlDEE. CHRlST ALMlGHTY.
WHO THE HELL ARE WE.
ZlM-ZAM. GODDAMN.
WE'RE AlRBORNE lNFANTRY.
SO. DO WE FEEL LlKE
WE'RE READY TO BE
ARMY PARATROOPERS?
( together )
YES. SERGEANT.
I HOPE SO.
THlS'LL BE THE
FlRST OF FlVE EXlTS
FROM A C47 AlRCRAFT
SCHEDULED FOR TODAY.
GET READY.
STAND UP.
HOOK UP.
( Sargeant )
UPON SUCCESSFUL COMPLETlON
OF YOUR FlFTH AND FlNAL JUMP.
YOU'LL BE CERTlFlED
ARMY PARATROOPERS.
CHECK EQUlPMENT!
SOUND-OFF FOR
EQUlPMENT CHECK!
NlNE OKAY.
ElGHT OKAY.
SEVEN OKAY.
SlX OKAY.
FlVE OKAY.
FOUR OKAY.
THREE OKAY.
TWO OKAY.
ONE OKAY.
THERE'LL BE A LOT OF MEN
DROPPlNG FROM THE SKY TODAY.
HOPEFULLY. UNDER
DEPLOYED CANOPlES.
STAND lN THE DOOR!
I GUARANTEE YOU'RE GONNA
LOVE lT. LlEUTENANT.
GO. GO!
JUMPlNG FRO
IN STlCKS OF 12 JUMPERS
PER AlRCRAFT.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO lS
REMEMBER WHAT YOU WERE TAUGHT.
AND I GUARANTEE YOU GRAVlTY
WlLL TAKE CARE OF THE REST.
GO. GO. GO. GO!
GO. GO. GO!
DAMNlT.
AND. GENTLEMEN.
REST ASSURED.
ANY REFUSALS lN THE AlRCRAFT
OR AT THE DOOR...
AND I GUARANTEE YOU.
YOU WlLL...
BE OUT OF
THE AlRBORNE.
FOUR OKAY.
THREE OKAY.
TWO OKAY.
ONE OKAY.
STAND lN THE DOOR.
GO!
1.000. 2.000. 3.000.
4.000. 5.000. 6.000.
7.000. 8.000. 9.000!
( cheering )
Hl-HO. SlLVER.
NOW JUST THlNK. lF YOU HAD
ANY CLASS OR STYLE LlKE ME.
SOMEBODY MlGHT
MlSTAKE YOU FOR SOMEBODY.
YOU MEAN LlKE YOUR
FUCKlNG SERGEANT?
I'M JUST KlDDlNG.
CONGRATULATlONS.
MARTlN.
CORPORAL TOYE. THERE WlLL BE
NO LEANlNG lN MY COMPANY.
ARE THOSE DUSTY
JUMP WlNGS?
HOW DO YOU EXPECT TO
SLAY THE HUNS
WlTH DUST ON
YOUR JUMP WlNGS?
LUZ. JUST GlVE
ME A DRlNK.
HELL OF AN lDEA. JOE.
THERE YOU GO.
THREE MlLES UP.
THREE MlLES DOWN.
TEN-HUT!
WELL. AT EASE.
PARATROOPERS.
GOOD EVENlNG.
"EASY COMPANY".
EVENlNG. SlR.
NOW. PARACHUTE lNFANTRY
lS A BRAND NEW CONCEPT
IN AMERlCAN
MlLlTARY HlSTORY.
BUT BY GOD. THE 506 lS GONNA
FORGE THAT BRAND NEW CONCEPT
INTO VlCTORY.
YES. SlR.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
l'M DAMNED PROUD
OF EACH AND EVERY
ONE OF YOU.
NOW. YOU DESERVE
THlS PARTY.
THANK YOU.
SERGEANT GRANT.
SlR.
SO. I WANT YOU
TO HAVE FUN...
AND REMEMBER
OUR MOTTO...
CURRAHEE!
( cheering )
PETTY.
MAP.
C'MON.
AH. CHRlST.
WE'RE lN THE
WRONG POSlTlON.
WE'RE TEXTBOOK POSlTlON
FOR AMBUSH. SlR.
WE SHOULD SlT TlGHT.
LET THE ENEMY TEAM COME
lNTO OUR KlLLlNG ZONE.
THEY'RE RlGHT OUT
THERE SOMEWHERE.
LET'S JUST
GET 'EM.
SlR. WE HAVE
PERFECT COVER HERE.
LlEUTENANT.
DEPLOY YOUR TROOPS.
2nd PLATOON.
MOVE OUT.
WHAT?
TACTlCAL COLUMN.
CAPTAlN. YOU'VE
JUST BEEN KlLLED.
ALONG WlTH 95 PERCENT
OF YOUR COMPANY.
YOUR OUTFlT?
"EASY COMPANY".
2nd BATTALlON 506th.
LEAVE THREE WOUNDED
MEN ON THE GROUND
AND REPORT BACK TO
THE ASSEMBLY AREA.
GODDAMMlT.
YOU. YOU. YOU.
WELL. WHAT ARE
YOU GONNA DO?
NOTHlNG. JUST KEEP
TRAlNlNG THE MEN.
AM I lNTERRUPTlNG?
NO. NO.
LlEUTENANT LEWlS NlXON.
LlEUTENANT HARRY WELSH.
JUST lN FROM THE 82nd.
CONGRATULATlONS
ON THE PROMOTlON.
AH. THANKS. lF YOU
WANNA CALL lT THAT.
YOU'LL LEARN HlM
PRETTY QUlCKLY.
NO FLAWS. NO VlCES.
NO SENSE OF HUMOR.
JUST LlKE YOUR CHUMS
UP AT BATTALlON STAFF.
WHAT'S UP?
I'M HEARlNG A LOT
OF RUMBLlNGS.
SOBEL?
JUST TALKlNG
ABOUT THAT.
SO. HE GETS A LlTTLE
JUMPY lN THE FlELD?
HMM-MMM.
HE GETS JUMPY AND
THEN YOU GET KlLLED.
THAT'S NlCE.
YEAH. LlSTEN.
lF WE DlSCUSS lT.
I THlNK lT SHOULD JUST
BE AMONGST OURSELVES.
OH. ABSOLUTELY.
2nd PLATOON READY?
READY. SlR.
THEN GET THEM
lN FORMATlON.
WE'RE MOVlNG OUT.
YES. SlR.
( laughing )
SHUT UP. COBB.
EH. YOU GOTTA
ADMlT lT.
HE'S GOT
NO CHANCE.
ElTHER THE KRAUTS
WlLL GET HlM.
OR ONE OF US.
WHO. SOBEL?
HE SCREWED UP
ONE MANEUVER.
WELL. YOU KNOW.
l'M ALWAYS FUMBLlNG
WlTH GRENADES.
IT WOULD BE EASY
lF ONE WENT OFF BY
ACClDENT. YOU KNOW?
WELL. NOW THEY
MUST HAVE PUT HlM lN
CHARGE FOR A REASON.
YEAH. 'CAUSE THE
ARMY WOULDN'T MAKE A
MlSTAKE. RlGHT. SHlFT?
GOlNG MY WAY?
WHEREVER THE TRAlN
TAKES ME.
WHERE DO YOU SUPPOSE
THAT MlGHT BE?
I HAVEN'T
GOT A CLUE.
YEAH. C'MON.
TAKE A GUESS.
ATLANTlC. PAClFlC.
ATLANTlC?
I'M NOT THE
lNTELLlGENCE OFFlCER.
MMM.
WELL. AS SUCH.
I OF COURSE KNOW.
BUT lF I TOLD YOU.
I'D HAVE TO KlLL YOU.
SO. DON'T TELL ME.
NEW YORK ClTY.
TROOP SHlP.
ENGLAND.
WE'RE lNVADlNG EUROPE.
MY FRlEND.
FORTRESS EUROPA.
SlNCE WHEN
DO I DRlNK?
IF I THOUGHT YOU'D
DRlNK lT. I WOULDN'T
OFFER lT TO YOU.
NlX?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WHEN YOU GET lNTO COMBAT?
OH. I HAVE EVERY CONFlDENCE
lN MY SCROUNGlNG ABlLlTlES.
AND I HAVE A CASE OF VAT 69
HlDDEN lN YOUR FOOTLOCKER.
REALLY?
OH. YEAH.
MORNlNG.
MMM.
THlS COULD
TURN lNTO A
REAL NlCE TRlP.
( Sobel )
"DEAR SlR OR MADAM.
"SOON YOUR SON WlLL
DROP FROM THE SKY
"TO ENGAGE AND
DEFEAT THE ENEMY.
"YOUR FREQUENT LETTERS OF
LOVE AND ENCOURAGEMENT
"WlLL ARM HlM
WlTH A FlGHTlNG HEART.
"WlTH THAT HE CANNOT FAlL.
BUT WlLL WlN GLORY FOR HlMSELF.
"MAKE YOU PROUD OF HlM
AND HlS COUNTRY EVER GRATEFUL
"FOR HlS SERVlCE
lN lTS HOUR OF NEED.
SlGNED HERBERT M. SOBEL.
CAPTAlN COMMANDlNG."
RlGHT NOW. SOME LUCKY BASTARD'S
HEADED FOR THE SOUTH PAClFlC.
OH. WHAT l'D GlVE.
HE'S GONNA GET BlLLETED
ON SOME TROPlCAL lSLAND...
KEEP TALKlNG.
SlTTlNG UNDER A PALM TREE
WlTH SlX NAKED NATlVE GlRLS.
HELPlNG HlM
CUT UP COCONUTS
SO HE CAN HAND-FEED 'EM
TO THE FLAMlNGOS.
FLAMlNGOS ARE MEAN.
THEY BlTE.
SO DO THE NAKED
NATlVE GlRLS.
WlTH ANY LUCK.
HEY. GUYS. l'M GLAD
l'M GOlNG TO EUROPE.
HlTLER GETS ONE OF THESE
RlGHT ACROSS THE WlNDPlPE.
ROOSEVELT CHANGES THANKSGlVlNG
TO JOE TOYE DAY.
AND PAYS ME 10 GRAND
A YEAR FOR THE REST
OF MY FUCKlNG LlFE.
WHAT lF WE DON'T
GET TO EUROPE?
WHAT lF THEY SEND US
TO NORTH AFRlCA?
MY BROTHER'S
lN NORTH AFRlCA.
HE SAYS lT'S HOT.
REALLY. lT'S HOT
lN AFRlCA?
SHUT UP.
THE POlNT lS. lT DON'T
MATTER WHERE WE GO.
ONCE WE GET lNTO COMBAT.
THE ONLY PERSON YOU CAN TRUST
IS YOURSELF AND THE
FELLA NEXT TO YOU.
HEY. AS LONG AS
HE'S A PARATROOPER.
OH. YEAH?
AND WHAT lF THAT PARATROOPER
TURNS OUT TO BE SOBEL?
IF l'M NEXT TO SOBEL
lN COMBAT. l'M MOVlNG
ON DOWN THE LlNE.
HOOK UP WlTH
SOME OTHER OFFlCER.
LlKE HEYLlGER
OR WlNTERS.
I LlKE WlNTERS.
HE'S A GOOD MAN.
BUT WHEN THE BULLETS
START FLYlNG.
I DON'T KNOW lF l
WANT A QUAKER DOlNG
MY FlGHTlNG FOR ME.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
HE'S A QUAKER?
HE AlN'T CATHOLlC.
NElTHER'S SOBEL.
THAT PRlCK'S
THE SON OF ABRAHAM.
HE'S WHAT?
HE'S A JEW.
I'M A JEW.
CONGRATULATlONS.
GET YOUR NOSE
OUT OF MY FACE.
WHAT'S ALL
THAT ABOUT?
GONORRHEA CALLED
SOBEL A JEW.
LlEBGOTT TOOK OFFENSE
'CAUSE HE'S A JEW TOO.
FlGHTlNG OVER SOBEL.
THAT'S SMART.
ATTACK!
NO. YOU WANNA
KlLL HlM!
PARRY RlGHT.
PARRY LEFT.
THRUST!
TAKE COVER.
OKAY.
YESTERDAY. WE TALKED ABOUT
MAGNETlC DECLlNATlON
AND THE LEFT ADD.
RlGHT SUBTRACT RULE.
TODAY WE'RE GONNA
PUT lT lNTO PRACTlCE.
THERE ARE TWO BASlC TYPES
OF FlGHTlNG POSlTlONS.
THE FlRST lS
THE PREPARED POSlTlON.
THE ADVANTAGES
OF A PREPARED POSlTlON
ARE THAT lT GlVES YOU
COVER AND CONCEALMENT.
COMMENCE FlRE!
WE'LL THEN MANEUVER.
RlGHT lN THROUGH
THESE TREES.
AT THE SAME TlME.
OUR 2nd PLATOON.
IN THlS PARTlCULAR CASE.
MOVES OVER HERE.
HE'S THEN GONNA CLOSE
WlTH AND KlLL OR
CAPTURE THAT GERMAN.
( panting )
SOBEL'S LATE.
WHY lS THERE
A FENCE HERE?
THERE SHOULD BE
NO FENCE HERE.
TlPPER!
YES. SlR.
GlVE ME THE MAP.
PERCONTE. LUZ.
GET THE MEN.
GET 'EM B--
TAKE COVER BEHlND
THOSE TREES.
ALRlGHT. YOU
HEARD THE WORD.
THERE SHOULD BE
NO. THERE SHOULD
BE NO FENCE HERE.
UM...
( clearing throat )
WE COULD GO
OVER lT. SlR.
REALLY?
THAT'S NOT THE POlNT.
WHERE ARE THE GODDAMN--
WHERE THE GODDAMN
HELL ARE WE?
PERCONTE?
YEAH.
SOBEL'S LOST AGAlN.
RlGHT?
YEAH. HE'S LOST.
FUCKlNG CHRlST.
CAN YOU DO
MAJOR HORTON?
( as John Wayne )
DOES A WlLD BEAR CRAP
lN THE WOODS. SON?
SHH. SHH. SHH.
MAYBE THE GOOD
MAJOR CAN GOOSE
THlS SCHMUCK.
GET US MOVlNG?
NO WAY...
OH YEAH. YES.
YOU GOTTA.
ALRlGHT.
JUST THlS ONCE.
SHH. SHH.
THREE FlVE.
SlX. ElGHT.
THREE. THREE.
ISN'T THAT
THE lNTERSECTlON?
NO. SlR. lT'S HERE.
YOU'RE A FULL
GRlD OFF.
GODDAMMlT.
IS THERE A PROBLEM.
CAPTAlN SOBEL?
WHO SAlD THAT?
WHO BROKE SlLENCE?
I THlNK lT'S
MAJOR HORTON. SlR.
MAJOR HORTON?
WHAT lS HE.
DlD HE JOlN US?
I THlNK MAYBE HE'S MOVlNG
BETWEEN THE PLATOONS. SlR.
WHAT lS THE GODDAMN
HOLDUP. MR. SOBEL?
A FENCE. SlR.
UM. GOD...
A BARBED WlRE FENCE.
OH. THAT DOG
JUST AlN'T GONNA HUNT.
NOW. YOU CUT THAT FENCE
AND GET THlS GODDAMN PLATOON
ON THE MOVE!
YES. SlR!
WHERE ARE MY GODDAMN
WlRE CUTTERS?
WE HAVE TO MOVE.
SlR. WlTHOUT CAPTAlN
SOBEL AND 1 st PLATOON?
IT'S A "T" lNTERSECTlON.
WE lMPROVlSE.
DOUBLE ENVELOPMENT
LAlD ON A BASE OF FlRE
TO CUT THE ROAD
lN ALL DlRECTlONS.
HOOK RlGHT
WlTH 1 st SQUAD.
TELL GUARNERE TO
MOVE LEFT WlTH 2nd.
I'LL BE RlGHT UP
THE MlDDLE WlTH 3rd. GO.
YES. SlR.
DEARY ME.
( dog barking )
BLOODY HELL.
YOU'VE DONE
lT NOW. YANKS.
YOU'VE CAPTURED ME.
Hl-HO. SlLVER!
WOULD THAT BE
THE ENEMY?
AS A MATTER
OF FACT. YES.
GOOD WORK.
2nd PLATOON.
WE TOOK
THE OBJECTlVE.
WHO lS THE lDlOT WHO
CUT THAT MAN'S FENCE?
I WAS ORDERED TO. SlR.
BY WHOM?
MAJOR HORTON. SlR.
MAJOR HORTON?
YES. SlR.
MAJOR HORTON
TOLD YOU TO DO THAT?
YES. SlR.
MAJOR HORTON ORDERED
YOU TO CUT THE FENCE?
YES. HE DlD.
MAJOR HORTON lS ON
LEAVE lN LONDON.
GET THOSE COWS
OUT OF HERE.
LlEUTENANT WlNTERS.
WlTH CAPTAlN SOBEL'S
COMPLlMENTS. SlR.
LlEUTENANT.
OH. FOR CRYlNG
OUT LOUD.
THlS SPELLS
COURT-MARTlAL.
NO. SlR.
I DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
YOUR ORDERS TO
ME WERE TO lNSPECT
THE LATRlNES
AT 1000 HOURS.
FROM 0930 TO 0955
I WAS CENSORlNG
THE ENLlSTED MEN'S MAlL
BY ORDER OF
COLONEL STRAYER.
AT 1000 HOURS I FOLLOWED
YOUR ORDERS TO THE MlNUTE.
I CHANGED THAT
TlME TO 0945.
NO ONE
TOLD ME. SlR.
I TELEPHONED.
I'M QUARTERED WlTH A FAMlLY
THAT HAS NO TELEPHONE.
AND SENT A RUNNER.
NO RUNNER FOUND
ME. CAPTAlN.
IRREGARDLESS. WHEN GlVEN
A TASK TO PERFORM
BY A RANKlNG OFFlCER
TO ANOTHER OFFlCER.
YOU FAlLED TO DO SO.
WERE I TO LET
SUCH A FAlLURE OF DUTY
BY MY OWN XO GO UNPUNlSHED.
WHAT KlND OF MESSAGE
lS THAT TO THE MEN?
I PERFORMED MY DUTY
AS I WAS ORDERED. SlR.
AND I DlSAGREE.
SO. YOUR OPTlONS ARE
QUlTE SlMPLE. LlEUTENANT.
PUNlSHMENT FOR YOUR OFFENSES
WlLL BE DENlAL OF
A 48-HOUR PASS
FOR 60 DAYS.
STAND BEFORE ME
AT ATTENTlON.
OR YOU MAY lNlTlATE
A LETTER OF APPEAL
AND REQUEST A TRlAL
BY COURT-MARTlAL.
YOU SPEND YOUR WEEKENDS
ON THE BASE ANYWAY. DlCK.
BE A MAN.
TAKE THE PUNlSHMENT.
MAY I BORROW
YOUR PEN. SlR?
MY ENDORSEMENT. SlR.
I REQUEST TRlAL
BY COURT-MARTlAL.
WE LOST WlNTERS
TO BATTALlON MESS.
YOU'RE SHlTTlNG ME.
NO.
STRAYER DlD lT. WHlLE THEY TRY
TO FlGURE OUT THE PROCEDURES
FOR HlS COURT-MARTlAL.
WELL. NlX BETTER
FlND A LOOPHOLE
AND GET HlM OUT.
AND lF HE DON'T?
WlNTERS SCRAMBLES EGGS
WHlLE THE REST OF US MAKE
THE BlG JUMP WlTH SOBEL.
NOT ME.
SO WE'RE GOlNG THROUGH
WlTH THlS. RlGHT?
WE'VE GOTTA
DO SOMETHlNG.
YEAH.
ALRlGHT.
GOOD.
BUT WE'D ALL BETTER
BE CLEAR OF THE
CONSEQUENCES.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE CONSEQUENCES.
WE COULD BE LlNED UP
AGAlNST A WALL AND SHOT.
NOW. l'M READY
TO FACE THAT.
AND EVERY ONE OF US
HAD BETTER BE. TOO.
I WlLL NOT FOLLOW
THAT MAN lNTO COMBAT.
ME NElTHER.
ALRlGHT.
THEN LET'S DO lT.
I HEREBY...
NO LONGER...
WlSH TO SERVE...
AS A NON-COMMlSSlONED
OFFlCER...
IN "EASY COMPANY".
ALRlGHT. BOYS.
GOOD LUCK.
I OUGHT TO HAVE
YOU ALL SHOT!
THlS lS NOTHlNG LESS
THAN AN ACT OF MUTlNY
WHlLE WE PREPARE FOR THE
GODDAMN lNVASlON OF EUROPE.
SERGEANT HARRlS.
YES. SlR.
TURN lN YOUR STRlPES.
COLLECT YOUR GEAR.
YOU ARE HEREBY TRANSFERRED
OUT OF MY REGlMENT.
YES. SlR.
GET OUT.
SERGEANT RANNEY.
SlR.
YOU CONSlDER YOURSELF
LUCKY. l'M ONLY
BUSTlNG YOU TO PRlVATE.
ALL OF YOU NCOs
HAVE DlSGRACED
THE 101st AlRBORNE.
YOU CAN CONSlDER
YOURSELF LUCKY THAT
WE ARE ON THE EVE
OF THE LARGEST
ACTlON lN THE
HlSTORY OF WARFARE.
WHlCH LEAVES ME
NO CHOlCE. BUT TO
SPARE YOUR LlVES.
NOW. GET OUT OF MY OFFlCE
AND GET OUT OF MY SlGHT.
GET.
KEEP 'EM COMlNG.
THAT-A-BOY.
THAT'S lT.
I CAN ONLY
SPECULATE. SlR.
MOST OF THE MEN WOULD.
WOULD NEVER DO THlS.
BUT I BELlEVE JUST
A FEW OF THE SERGEANTS
MAY HAVE FELT
THElR LOYALTY LAY
MORE TO THE PLATOON
THAN TO THE COMPANY.
AND THESE FEW SERGEANTS
CONVlNCED ALL OF THE OTHER
NCOs lN YOUR COMPANY
TO TURN lN
THElR STRlPES?
AS STAFF SERGEANTS.
THEY HAVE A GREAT AMOUNT
OF lNFLUENCE. SlR.
BUT AS I SAY.
THE REST ARE GOOD MEN.
I KNOW THEM.
I CAN WORK WlTH THEM.
THlS BUSlNESS WlTH
THE WlNTERS' COURT-MARTlAL
HAS BEEN AN
UNPLEASANT DlSTRACTlON.
INDEED. lNDEED
lT HAS. SlR.
HOWEVER...
YOUR COMMAND
OF "EASY COMPANY"
HAS BEEN EXEMPLARY.
THANK. THANK
YOU. SlR.
IN FACT. EXCEPT FOR
THE ACTlONS OF A
FEW OF YOUR NONCOMS.
I BELlEVE YOU'VE FlELDED
ONE OF THE FlNEST
COMPANlES OF SOLDlERS
I'VE EVER SEEN.
YES. SlR.
HERBERT. DlVlSlON
HAS ESTABLlSHED
A PARACHUTE TRAlNlNG
SCHOOL AT CHlLTON FOLlAT.
THE lDEA lS FOR
NON-lNFANTRY TYPES WHO...
WERE VlTAL TO
THE COMlNG lNVASlON.
SUCH AS DOCTORS AND CHAPLAlNS.
TO TAKE JUMP TRAlNlNG THERE.
FRANKLY. I CAN'T THlNK
OF ANYONE MORE
QUALlFlED TO COMMAND
SUCH A SCHOOL
THAN YOU ARE.
SlR?
I'M REASSlGNlNG YOU
TO CHlLTON FOLlAT.
I'M LOSlNG
"EASY COMPANY"?
THE WAR EFFORT
NEEDS YOU ELSEWHERE.
PERMlSSlON TO
SPEAK. SlR?
GRANTED.
IS. WHO. WHO WlLL
BE REPLAClNG ME?
LlEUTENANT MEEHAN FROM
BAKER COMPANY lS SENlOR.
GOOD LUCK AT
CHlLTON FOLlAT. HERBERT.
DON'T LET US
DOWN NOW.
NO. SlR.
CARRY ON.
( male )
2nd PLATOON.
LlSTEN UP.
I WANT THE 1st
SQUAD AND A-SlDE
TENTS RlGHT UP THERE.
3rd SQUAD.
SECOND ROW...
HOLY SHlT.
NO. lT'S ALL RlGHT.
MATE. WE'RE TOMMlES.
NOT BLEEDlN' BOSCH.
IS ALL THlS REAL?
YEAH. YEAH.
WELL. SOME OF lT'S
FROM THE HERMANS.
THAT SOMEBODY'S
TAlLORS KNOCKED UP.
FOR YOU LADS. ACTUALLY. SO.
YOU CAN GET YOUR MlNCE PlES
ON SOME OF THlS
JERRY CLOBBER. lF YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
NOT REALLY.
EH?
HEY. MAC.
YOU GOT A LUGER?
I'M DYlNG TO GET MY
HANDS ON A REAL LUGER.
YEAH. GO ON THEN.
QUlCK BUTCHERS. YEAH?
BOY. SHE SURE
lS A DOOZY.
YEAH. lT'S
PUKKA. lNNlT.
WHAT?
HEY. PETTY.
HEY. MATE.
YOU'RE HAVlNG A BATH
lF YOU THlNK YOU'RE
HALF-lNCHlNG THAT.
OH. YEAH.
SORRY.
WELL. GOOD LUCK.
YOU TOO. MATE.
WHAT'S UP. HOOBS?
THESE MEN HAVE BEEN THROUGH
THE TOUGHEST TRAlNlNG
THE ARMY
HAS TO OFFER.
UNDER THE WORST
POSSlBLE ClRCUMSTANCES.
AND THEY VOLUNTEERED
FOR lT.
CHRlST. DlCK. I WAS JUST
SHOOTlNG CRAPS WlTH THEM.
IT'S NOT LlKE...
YOU KNOW WHY
THEY VOLUNTEERED?
SO. WHEN THlNGS GOT
REALLY BAD THE MAN
lN THE FOXHOLE
NEXT TO THEM
WOULD BE THE BEST.
NOT SOME DRAFTEE WHO'S
GONNA GET HlM KlLLED.
ARE YOU TlCKED
BECAUSE THEY LlKE ME?
BECAUSE l'M SPENDlNG TlME
TO GET TO KNOW MY SOLDlERS?
I MEAN. C'MON. YOU'VE BEEN
WlTH THESE GUYS FOR. WHAT.
TWO YEARS?
I'VE BEEN HERE
FOR SlX DAYS.
YOU'RE GAMBLlNG. BOB.
SO WHAT.
SOLDlERS DO THAT.
I DON'T DESERVE
A REPRlMAND FOR lT.
WHAT lF YOU'D WON?
WHAT?
( slowly )
WHAT-lF-YOU'D-WON?
NEVER PUT YOURSELF
lN A POSlTlON
WHERE YOU CAN TAKE
FROM THESE MEN.
LlEUTENANT MEEHAN?
ENTER.
ON THE LAST TRAlNlNG
JUMP. I HAD A COMPASS.
CLOSE THE FLAP.
THEN WE TURN LEFT.
YEAH.
BEARlNG ZERO FOUR TWO.
12 MlNUTES.
THEN ANOTHER LEFT?
YES.
YEAH.
CALL lT THREE
FlVE ElGHT.
FOR 10 AND
A HALF MlNUTES.
GREEN LlGHT.
RlGHT OVER RAMSBURY.
RAMSBURY.
EVERY SlNGLE TlME.
LlNEAR DlSTANCE ON
THE GRlD OF ABOUT...
OKAY.
RAMSBURY.
UPOTTERY.
SO...
IT'S NORMANDY.
( Nixon )
ST. MARlE DU MONT.
CAUSEWAY NUMBER ONE.
CAUSEWAY NUMBER TWO.
THE ULTlMATE
FlELD PROBLEM.
THE ESTUARY OF
THE DOUVE RlVER
DlVlDES TWO BEACHHEADS.
CODE-NAMED UTAH. HERE.
AND OMAHA. HERE.
SEABORNE lNFANTRY WlLL
HlT THESE BEACHES lN FORCE
AT A DATE AND TlME
TO BE SPEClFlED.
H-HOUR. D-DAY.
AlRBORNE'S OBJECTlVE.
GENTLEMEN.
IS TO TAKE THE TOWN OF
CARELTAN. OR CARENTAN.
THUS LlNKlNG UTAH AND
OMAHA lNTO A SlNGLE
CONTlNUOUS BEACHHEAD.
... LlNKlNG OMAH AND UTAH
lNTO ONE CONTlNUOUS BEACHHEAD.
EACH TROOPER WlLL
LEARN THlS OPERATlON BY HEART
AND KNOW HlS AND EVERY
OTHER OUTFlTS' MlSSlON
TO THE DETAlL.
LlEUTENANT MEEHAN?
YES. DUKEMAN.
SlR. ARE WE
DROPPlNG TONlGHT?
WHEN lT'S TlME FOR YOU TO
KNOW. WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
IN THE MEANTlME.
STUDY THESE SAND
TABLES. MAPS.
AND RECONNAlSSANCE PHOTOS
UNTlL YOU CAN DRAW A MAP
OF THE AREA BY MEMORY.
NOW. WE WlLL DROP
BEHlND THlS ATLANTlC WALL
FlVE HOURS BEFORE
THE 4th lNFANTRY
LANDS AT UTAH.
AND BETWEEN OUR
ASSEMBLY AREA AND THE
BATTALlON'S OBJECTlVE.
THERE lS
A GERMAN GARRlSON
RlGHT HERE lN THlS AREA.
ST. MARlE DU MONT.
"EASY COMPANY" WlLL
DESTROY THAT GARRlSON.
THREE DAY SUPPLY OF K-RATlONS.
CHOCOLATE BARS. CHARMS CANDY.
POWDERED COFFEE.
SUGAR. AND MATCHES.
COMPASS. BAYONET.
ENTRENCHlNG TOOL.
AMMUNlTlON. GAS MASK.
MUSETTE BAG WlTH AMMO.
MY WEBBlNG. MY.45. CANTEEN.
TWO CARTONS OF SMOKES.
HAWKlNS MlNE.
TWO GRENADES.
SMOKE GRENADE.
GAMMA GRENADE.
TNT.
THlS BULLSHlT.
AND A PAlR OF
NASTY SKlVVlES.
WHAT'S YOUR POlNT?
YOU KNOW. THlS STUFF
WElGHS AS MUCH AS I DO.
I'VE STlLL GOT MY CHUTE.
MY RESERVE CHUTE.
MY MAE WEST. MY M-1.
WHERE ARE YOU KEEPlNG
YOUR BRASS KNUCKLES?
I COULD USE SOME
BRASS KNUCKLES.
SERGEANT MARTlN.
HEY. VEST.
ANYTHlNG FOR ME?
NO.
SERGEANT MARTlN.
FOR TALBERT.
YOUR CONDOMS?
I DON'T KNOW.
PROBABLY.
WHAT YOU GOT?
"DEAR FLOYD.
GlVE 'EM HELL."
IT'S FROM CHlEF
OF THE KOKOMO
POLlCE DEPARTMENT.
RlGHT.
WHOA. YOU'VE
GOTTA LOVE COPS.
ALRlGHT. LlSTEN
UP. LlSTEN UP.
IF YOU DlD NOT SlGN YOUR
Gl LlFE lNSURANCE POLlCY.
YOU GO ON OVER
AND SEE SERGEANT EVANS
AT THE HEADQUARTERS
COMPANY TENT.
YOU BOYS DON'T
LET YOUR FAMlLlES
MlSS OUT ON
$10.000.
YOU HEAR THAT.
GERRY?
HEY. LlP?
YEAH. BOY.
HAS GUARNERE SAlD
ANYTHlNG TO YOU
ABOUT HlS BROTHER?
NO.
I GOT A PROBLEM.
MY WlFE KEEPS UP
WlTH THlNGS BACK HOME.
CASUALTY LlSTS
AND LlKE THAT.
YEAH?
GUARNERE'S BROTHER
lN lTALY?
HENRY?
KlLLED lN
MONTE CASSlNO.
WELL. l'M SURE
HE DOESN'T KNOW.
DAMN.
WHAT'D YOU THlNK
I SHOULD DO?
IF lT WERE ME.
l'D TELL HlM.
COUPLE OF HOURS
BEFORE WE JUMP?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHY THEY SPRlNGlNG
THESE THlNGS ON US NOW?
IT'S JUST AN EXTRA 80 POUNDS
STRAPPED TO YOUR LEG.
DOES ANYBODY HAVE ANY lDEA HOW
THE HELL THlS THlNG WORKS?
COLONEL SlNK.
"SOLDlERS OF
THE REGlMENT:
"TONlGHT lS THE NlGHT
"OF NlGHTS.
"TODAY. AS YOU READ THlS.
YOU ARE EN ROUTE
"TO THE GREAT
ADVENTURE FOR WHlCH
YOU HAVE TRAlNED FOR
OVER TWO YEARS."
SO. THAT'S WHY THEY
GAVE US lCE CREAM.
"EASY COMPANY".
LlSTEN UP!
CHANNEL COAST lS SOCKED
lN WlTH RAlN AND FOG.
NO JUMP TONlGHT.
THE lNVASlON
HAS BEEN POSTPONED.
WE'RE ON A 24-HOUR
STAND-DOWN.
Well. this is
quite a surprise.
Not particularly.
It so happens
I rather expected it.
Well. I can't see
how you people can
pass up $80.000
for the cause.
For whose cause?
If you're so interested
in serving a cause.
why don't you
join the army?
Next. please.
Oh. 4-M.
You look
1 -A to me.
Hey. you don't
look so bad yourself.
"DEAREST JOHNNY."
Well. should you
be giving blood?
I woke up.
I GOT THE WRONG
GODDAMN JACKET.
SHH.
I was struck
by lightning.
Nobody dancing.
It doesn't
matter.
"YOUR PAL. BlLL
GUARNERE'S BROTHER..."
( panting )
GOOD LUCK. LADS.
SEE YOU. TOMMY.
SEE YOU. MATE.
TRY AND GET THESE
LEG STRAPS THROUGH.
JOHNNY?
GOT SOMETHlNG
YOU MlGHT BE
LOOKlNG FOR.
TOOK YOUR JACKET
BY MlSTAKE.
I'M SORRY.
YOU READ lT?
WHERE THE FUCK lS
MONTE CASSlNO?
I DON'T KNOW.
ITALY SOMEWHERE.
SORRY ABOUT
YOUR BROTHER. BlLL
HE WAS. ER...
LET'S GET
THlS OVER WlTH.
BlLL?
I'LL MEET UP
WlTH YOU OVER THERE.
GENTLEMEN. DOC ROE
lS HANDlNG THESE
OUT FOR AlR SlCKNESS.
ORDERS ARE. EVERY MAN
TAKES ONE NOW.
ANOTHER 30 MlNUTES
lN THE AlR.
LlEUTENANT.
2nd PLATOON.
LlSTEN UP.
GOOD LUCK.
GOD BLESS YOU.
I'LL SEE YOU lN
THE ASSEMBLY AREA.
IF THE WlRE CONSTANT
lS SENSlTlVE.
THEN I THlNK ALL
WE SHOULD HAVE TO
DEAL WlTH lS...
GODDAMN. LlEB.
THAT AlRSlCK PlLL
lS MAKlNG ME LOOPY.
Captions Copyright 2001
HOME BOX OFFlCE
A Division of TlME WARNER
ENTERTAlNMENT COMPANY. L.P.
Captioned by
HBO COMMUNlCATlONS CENTE
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org